

# DIMAS IQBAL PRADANA

Full Stack Web Developer & UI/UX Enthusiast

Enthusiatic computer science graduated with a background in web design and development. Experienced in laravel applications development and passion in responsive website design. Committed to developing scallable web applications with a best practice across full stack.



## WEBSITE / PORTFOLIO

halfbun.github.io



## LINKEDIN

linkedin.com/in/halfbun



#### PHONE

+6285725656282



#### **EMAIL**

d.igbalpradana94@gmail.com



#### **ADDRESS**

Dukuh RT 05 RW III Karanggeneng, Boyolali Jawa Tengah 57312

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Freelance Web Developer & Digital Artist

Sept 2021-Now

- Online
- Designing and building personal or commercial website, such as personal website, portfolio, and company profiles.
- Making digital illustration and artwork as client requested, such as character design, and digital painting

#### IT Staff

Feb 2019 - Aug 2021 PT. Andalan Mandiri Busana, Karanganyar

- Monitoring and maintaining computer systems and networks
- Installing and configuring network and computer hardware, software, systems
- Responding in a timely manner to service issues and requests

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor Degree in Computer Science (GPA: 3.21)

2012-2018 Diponegoro University, Semarang, Indonesia

## Senior High School Graduate

2009-2012 SMA Negeri 1 Boyolali, Boyolali, Indonesia

Junior High Scholl Graduate

2006-2009 SMP Negeri 3 Boyolali, Boyolali, Indonesia

### **Elementary School Graduate**

2000-2006 SD Negeri 1 Karanggeneng, Boyolali, Indonesia

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### Infrastructure & Networking

- Software Troubleshooting & Installation (Proficient)
- Hardware Troubleshooting & Installation (Proficient)
- Data Management & Analysis (Intermediate)
- Physical/Digital IT Asset Management (Proficent)
- Network Management & Security: [Windows Server, Mikrotik, Network Installation & Troubleshooting, Cabling, VOIP] (Intermediate)

## Programming & Web Design

- Programming Language & Tools: [HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, Laravel, Bootstrap, MySQL] (Intermediate)
- Web Design: [Figma, Adobe XD] (Intermediate)

# CERTIFICATION

## **AWS Cloud Practitioner Essentials**

(Dicoding ~ Online)

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Back-End

(Dicoding ~ Online)

Become a Full-Stack Web Developer

(LinkedIn Learninng ~ Online)